大家好！这里是你们的好兄弟Carbot
我们刚上架这些新T恤
想购买的可以点击下方链接（简介里）
https://www.teepublic.com/stores/carbotanimation
其中一件是Zerg Hi，另外一件是为了艾尔
如果你没看出来的话——这是T恤上在叉子周围的字
还有一件是三个Marine，裂盔哥和补丁哥和医疗兵。
等等，我的意思是两个枪兵和医疗兵
限时发售，心动不如行动
嘿，我是你们的好朋友John Burton，来自Carbot animations.
有观众让我多做一些动画教学
今天安排上了
首先，我们所有的动画都是用Adobe Animate CC
你可以在adobe.com上找到
这不是恰饭视频
因此这完全是用爱发电
对我来说这款软件毫无难度
今天要做的动画是跑步循环
我们将以叉子的跑步动作为例
当你在创作跑步循环动画
尤其是在用An CC画跑步动作时
最重要的就是画出最夸张的姿势
比如一条胳膊尽可能靠前，一条腿尽可能向后。
画另外一对胳膊腿也是同样的道理
当你画完角色跑步的轮廓后
就可以进行下一步：把它变成一个元件(symbol)并且命名 (默认快捷键F8）
元件有自己的时间线并且会在整个主时间线上不断循环。
因此重用这个动作循环非常容易
如果角色需要跑过屏幕
你不需要重复每个步骤
只要你编辑好它的动画，就会一直循环它自己的动作
因此我所做的就是用很多图层
身体独立为一个图层
你画好身体之后
你可以创建一个新图层，再画一个从肩膀到身体上方的手臂
你就可以看到整个过程
完成手臂的绘画和上色工作后
我要把这个手臂也转换成元件
现在是元件套元件
工作有些进展了
双击这个元件
事实上我们又一次将它变成了元件
原因是我们想给这两条手臂加上动画
如果你这么做，就会自动将其变为元件
我们想确保元件的锚点在肩膀上
锚点就是此处的小白点
这就是元件的旋转中心点
决定了元件如何旋转、变形
我们要给元件增加 移动补间(motion tween) ...(作者口误)
总的来说就是要让手臂在最前和最后两个位置之间来回摆动
完成这步之后，我们就可以返回身体部分做另一只手臂的工作
这个循环的时长大概是10帧
因此所有动画长度都要是10帧，比如手臂来回摆动也是10帧
复制这个手臂
把它放到另一层，放置在身体后面
因为我们的循环是10帧
偏移最大的是第6帧
因此反方向手臂的动作从第六帧开始
方法是点击属性页面
将first选项参数改为6
这意味着它将从第六帧开始运动而不是第一帧
So I don't want to lose you guys here.
从第六帧开始的原因是：这个动作离第一帧最远
而不是第十帧离第一帧最远
第十帧的下一帧就是第一帧，因为整个过程会循环
第六帧是运动最远的一帧，它是动作过程的中点
这就是为什么你想让其中一只手臂从第六帧开始，而另一只从第一帧开始。
我会让两条手臂交错前后摆动
并循环这个过程
还要对两条腿做同样的操作
在前面这条腿和身体之间新建图层
画一条腿，转换为元件
这次，我们要让动画更加生动一些。
我们要做逐帧动画
这意味着我们要亲手画每一帧
这么做的原因是，膝盖和脚掌都会变形
因此为腿部做逐帧动画会更好
这样看上去就不会太僵硬，像真正在跑步一样。
If you do use a symbol which he can,
ah,
it'll just look a little bit more stiff,
which is fine when you're starting out,
so feel free to do the exact same thing that we do with the arms of the legs.
If you want to make it a little quick.
But I'm going to animate each leg frame by frame to show you how it's done,
and we're going to start with the key frames of the leg again,
that is the most forward frame and the furthest back frame and the most extreme frames are going to land on one and six.
So we do those first,
and then we do the in between,
which is every frame in between the key for,
and that's basically joining them slowly moving the way cross.
As you see,
a kind of the foot can have bends as it moves across the ground,
and the whole life changed a little bit of form.
So once we call it that we're actually going to exit the symbol and then we're going to copy that leg and make a new layer in between the body and the arm that is behind the body at this point,
if you press,
play back and you,
you've tasted the leg and you know it's going to look like the zealot is hopping on two feet.
This is what happens when you have an alternate alternated,
the animation and start one of the legs on the six frame and not the first.
So we're going to keep one leg on the first frame and the other leg.
Ah,
we're going to start at the six frame again.
Going to the properties tab,
you ought to make the right arm and the left leg in sync,
Meaning the right arms forward and the left leg is forward,
and vice versa.
With thee,
let the left arm,
and in the right leg,
they're going to be in sync with them,
being at the back that way and allow the xcel to run in a proper motion if you do the opposite,
if you have the right leg in the right arm forward,
it's going to look really,
really weird.
Ah,
and it obviously doesn't make any sense because it's like,
yeah,
it's like you're pulling your your legs with your arms and it looks not the way you wanted to look Basically,
so be sure to cycle the the limbs properly,
the opposing the right arm and left leg,
and vice versa,
starting on differ on the same frames and the other one's on frame.
Six If your run cycle is a phrase that it's going to be free from five,
if it's twenty frames,
then it's going to be framed eleven and so on.
That's going to be the middle frame to give this runs,
let go a little bit more off.
I save the circle of the chest as its own layer,
And so we're gonna,
make that into a symbol and we're going to squash and stretch it as the torso moves.
Ah slightly from left to right,
as is running,
you don't have to do this.
you could just draw the the circle in.
Ah,
I'm doing this as an additional option of how you can spice up the run.
So if you exit the symbol,
you can now see the run cycle looks pretty good,
You know,
it doesn't look too bad.
Ah,
and we can actually spices up a little more by turning the whole run cycle into another symbol,
and he'd call out whatever he wants.
The reason why we're going to do this is because right now he's running,
and he just is.
He's not bouncing whatsoever.
He's kind of almost like he's gliding along the ground.
It looks fine for a simple animation,
but if you do want to make it a little bit nicer,
you can do this as well.
So once you made the whole run cycle into an additional symbol,
we're in a right click and make it into a motion tween,
and we're going to make the zealot bounce up,
And down,
so in this timeline,
you want him to bounce up and down twice because there's two legs there that are alternating between the two,
so we're going to make the first frame and the last frame.
the exact same keefe ranges press at six.
I don't move yet.
then the middle frame again,
this is framed six.
Ah,
we are going to make that the exact same position as well,
so we could have six on the middle frame as well.
the frames in between these three dots.
Ah,
we can actually like.
I think it shows the frame three in frame.
seven We can drag the symbol down of bits.
Ah,
on both of those sprained three in frame.
seven.
If you play it back,
you can now see,
the zealot is bouncing a bit and even made a bounce forward,
not just up in a little bit forward,
not too much.
You don't want to do too much better than bouncing up as well.
Especially so,
if he acts of that symbol now,
now we have the salt bouncing up and down while he's running again,
some most of the time.
actually,
Almost every time I set it for good animation,
you just want to isolate each section,
so you're not trying to do everything all at once.
You can always adjust and add to the animation later on.
Make sure you do the proper planning,
so that's it guys.
That's how you do a pretty decent,
easy run cycle,
so run cycles are a little bit difficult,
especially when you're first starting animation.
It's because the limbs are kind of gone everywhere,
there need to be the opposite.
and I've seen plenty of people like they.
Kind of get confused,
of which live is where you can actually darken as I did in this animation,
the limbs that are on the behind the body.
Ah,
you could do that by selecting the symbols that are the lives behind the body,
the leg in the arm and going down to two to color,
and then clicking the dropdown and going to brightness and and adjusting the brightness to make it a little darker.
This will help you follow what the heck is going on,
or you can kind of just side here.
You change of his ability.
One more thing before we go,
we can do a bit of a macro.
Here is what we do with crowd shots.
if we want a lots of characters running it on screen and we don't want to continuously do new motion tweens to make a run across,
we can actually again make the zealots another symbol.
Ah,
his bouncing up and down run cycle,
and we can create that into a three second.
However,
many second now run run run across a screen animation,
which is super easy.
We just need to right,
click and make a motion tween and then go to the furthest frame and drag them across the screen.
So now,
when you exit out of the air out of that symbol again,
we're like inception ising here like crazy when she accepted that symbol,
you can now copy and paste that symbol shrink and grow,
put it behind in other frames,
and you have a beautiful crowd shot with proper perspective,
all adults are running the same speed,
but now their summer front summer behind and saves you a lot of time again.
I getting to know the programs that your animation and using it to your advantage can save you tons of time.
I did not do this at first when I first started animating in doing Youtube videos.
The more I do it,
the more time I save in the more I'm kicking myself that I should have done it before.
so that's it guys that thinks,
watch and hope you enjoyed the video hope mates heads.
Ah,
it is very technical.
are spending some time and wrapping your head around the technicalities of the program again will really help you understand it and make the program work for you.
So that is a basic run cycle.
Again,
you don't have to do the bouncing up and down thing.
He could have stopped halfway through this.
But those those two extra things are kind of icing on the cake,
making a little bit better and a little bit more effective in your animation,
so guys like videos described,
you'll like its stuff.
hope you enjoy it.
I'll let me know what you would like to see animation tutorials,
the future on for those who are interested.
I OK,
I best friend talk to you later.
We'll hang out this weekend.
Okay, bye-bye.